The red light's on The tape is rolling They're
telling me what words to say I'm trying to find
the man I was But he gets farther
every day
They want the polish
They want the gleam The safer version
Of the dream But all I hear Is a thin machine
Another part of their big C. It's just a hollow
sound. My voice is in the mix.
But the words are not my own. It's just a hollow
sound. Another plastic fix.
I'm singing all alone.
They're all afraid of the burning cross.
Terrified
Of what they lost So now they're sanding
Off the edge Pushing me back From the ledge It's
just a hollow sound My voice is in the mix
But the words are not my own It's just a hollow
sound Another plastic fix
I'm singing all alone
It's just a hollow sound
Oh, oh Hollow sound Oh, oh
It's just a hollow sound My voice is in the mix
But the words are not my own It's just a hollow
sound Another plastic fix
I'm singing out